A Guide to the Social Science Research Council records, Japanese Studies and Korean Studies, Record Group 3, Series 7 FA1775
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) grant and fellowship declinations and withdrawals, 1968-1996; 4; 3.42 Cubic Feet 9 document boxes: 9 letter size boxes
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1989-1990 declinations - Friman, H. Richard, 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 733)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1989-1990 declinations - Chance, Frank, 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 734)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1989-1990 withdrawals - Reed, Steven, 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 735)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1989-1990 withdrawals - Russell, John, 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 736)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1989-1990 declinations - Kim, Young Chin, 1987-1989 (Box 59, Folder 737)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1989-1990 declinations - Johnson, Elmer, 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 738)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1989-1990 declinations - Hsaio, Frank, 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 739)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1989-1990 declinations - Graybill, Maribeth, 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 740)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1989-1990 declinations - Moudoukoutas, Panos, 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 741)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1989-1990 declinations - Matthews, Richard, 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 742)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1989-1990 declinations - Lebra, Joyce, 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 743)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1989-1990 declinations - Lammers, Wayne, 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 744)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1989-1990 declinations - Kraft, Kenneth, 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 745)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1989-1990 declinations - Wilson, Michiko, 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 746)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1989-1990 declinations - Yasutomo, Dennis, 1988-1989 (Box 60, Folder 747)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1989-1990 declinations - Wilsford, David, 1988-1989 (Box 60, Folder 748)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1989-1990 declinations - Sanford, James, 1988-1989 (Box 60, Folder 749)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1989-1990 declinations - Otto, Dale, 1988-1989 (Box 60, Folder 750)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Yuan, Xue (Box 60, Folder 751)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Adolphson, Mikael (Box 60, Folder 752)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Alam, Bachtiar (Box 60, Folder 753)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Bobrowski, Paula (Box 60, Folder 754)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Bradford, Scott C. (Box 60, Folder 755)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Cameron, Louisa (Box 60, Folder 756)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Davidann, Jon T. (Box 60, Folder 757)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Elder, Mark (Box 60, Folder 758)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Hahn, Tomie (Box 60, Folder 759)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Iguchi, Haruo (Box 60, Folder 760)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Imai, Noboru (Box 60, Folder 761)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Izbicki, Joanne (Box 60, Folder 762)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Jang, Wonho (Box 60, Folder 763)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Kawai, Miho (Box 60, Folder 764)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Kawakubo, Shigeko (Box 60, Folder 765)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Lo, Ming-cheng (Box 60, Folder 766)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Lohrentz, David (Box 60, Folder 767)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Meyerson, Christopher (Box 60, Folder 768)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Min, Byung-Il (Box 60, Folder 769)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Moen, Darrell G. (Box 60, Folder 770)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Mori, Junko (Box 60, Folder 771)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Nathan, Jeffrey H. (Box 60, Folder 772)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Nishikawa, Tomoji, circa 1994 (Box 60, Folder 773)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Nornes, Mark (Box 60, Folder 774)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Okita, Yoko (Box 60, Folder 775)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Okumura, Koji (Box 60, Folder 776)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Oniki, Shunji (Box 60, Folder 777)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Pringle, Patricia (Box 60, Folder 778)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Reichert, James R. (Box 60, Folder 779)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Sakamoto, Takayuki (Box 60, Folder 780)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Sedgwick, Mitchell (Box 60, Folder 781)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Shapiro, Ruth A. (Box 60, Folder 782)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Suenaga, Shizuko (Box 60, Folder 783)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Tackney, Charles (Box 60, Folder 784)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Takano, Shoji (Box 60, Folder 785)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Tinsley, Catherine (Box 60, Folder 786)
  - Joint Commitee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Togo, Ken (Box 60, Folder 787)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Vincent, John C. (Box 60, Folder 788)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Yamashita, Yoshie (Box 60, Folder 789)
  - Joint Commitee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Yang, Hongqiu (Box 60, Folder 790)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Yasutake, Rumi (Box 60, Folder 791)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1993-1994 declinations - Yoshimoto, Yasushi (Box 60, Folder 792)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1993-1994 declinations - Bevis, William W. (Box 60, Folder 793)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1993-1994 declinations - Cogann, Frances B. (Box 60, Folder 794)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1993-1994 declinations - Copeland, Rebecca (Box 60, Folder 795)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1993-1994 declinations - Elleman, Bruce (Box 60, Folder 796)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1993-1994 declinations - Ensign, Margee M. (Box 60, Folder 797)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1993-1994 declinations - Gelb, Joyce (Box 60, Folder 798)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1993-1994 declinations - Gottfried, Heidi (Box 60, Folder 799)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1993-1994 declinations - Huang, Xiaoming (Box 60, Folder 800)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1993-1994 declinations - Kishima, Takako (Box 60, Folder 801)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1993-1994 declinations - Large, Gerald (Box 60, Folder 802)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1993-1994 withdrawals - Lincoln, James R. (Box 60, Folder 803)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1993-1994 declinations - Machida, Soho K. (Box 60, Folder 804)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1993-1994 declinations - Maynard, Senko K. (Box 60, Folder 805)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1993-1994 declinations - Miller, Mara (Box 60, Folder 806)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1993-1994 declinations - Quander, Linda D. (Box 60, Folder 807)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1993-1994 declinations - Rabson, Steve (Box 60, Folder 808)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1993-1994 declinations - Robinson, Patricia (Box 60, Folder 809)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1993-1994 declinations - Scheiner, Irwin (Box 60, Folder 810)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1993-1994 declinations - Suranovic, Steven (Box 60, Folder 811)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1993-1994 declinations - Thorton, Sybil A. (Box 60, Folder 812)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1993-1994 declinations - Tsujimura, Natsuko (Box 60, Folder 813)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1993-1994 declinations - Wallace, John R. (Box 60, Folder 814)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Aiba, Keiko (Box 60, Folder 815)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Aoyama, Yuko (Box 60, Folder 816)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Benfell, Steven (Box 60, Folder 817)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Branstetter, Lee (Box 60, Folder 818)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Corning, Gregory (Box 60, Folder 819)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Elder, Mark (Box 60, Folder 820)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Ito, Masayuki (Box 60, Folder 821)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Johnson, David (Box 60, Folder 822)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Kaneko, Masayo (Box 60, Folder 823)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Kaneshiro, Edith (Box 60, Folder 824)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Kawabata, Eiji (Box 60, Folder 825)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Kim, Keunsei (Box 60, Folder 826)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Kutsuzawa, Kiyomi (Box 60, Folder 827)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Lu, Yuxin (Box 60, Folder 828)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Machino, Kazuo (Box 60, Folder 829)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Matsumura, Kyoko (Box 60, Folder 830)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Mayes, Patricia (Box 60, Folder 831)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Meyerson, Christopher (Box 60, Folder 832)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Miller, Meg (Box 60, Folder 833)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Miyashita, Akitoshi (Box 60, Folder 834)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Miura, Noriko (Box 60, Folder 835)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Muromatsu, Keiko (Box 60, Folder 836)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - O'Neill-Brown, Patricia (Box 60, Folder 837)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Otsubo, Sumiko (Box 61, Folder 838)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Raadschelders, Julie B. (Box 61, Folder 839)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Ratliff, John (Box 61, Folder 840)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Richter, Giles (Box 61, Folder 841)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Rousseau, Julie (Box 61, Folder 842)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Sato, Shigeki (Box 61, Folder 843)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Shapiro, Ruth (Box 61, Folder 844)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Simeon, Roblyn (Box 61, Folder 845)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Slater, David (Box 61, Folder 846)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Slaymaker, Doug (Box 61, Folder 847)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Smith, Donald (Box 61, Folder 848)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Stavely, David (Box 61, Folder 849)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Subramanian, Mukund (Box 61, Folder 850)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Takano, Shoji (Box 61, Folder 851)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Takeishi, Shoji (Box 61, Folder 852)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Toossi, Medhi (Box 61, Folder 853)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Wakabayashi, Tomoko (Box 61, Folder 854)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Witteveen, G. Peter (Box 61, Folder 855)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Xue, Yuan (Box 61, Folder 856)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Yamamoto, Genzo (Box 61, Folder 857)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Yang, Daqing (Box 61, Folder 858)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Yeh, Christine (Box 61, Folder 859)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1994-1995 declinations - Yoshida, Yukiko (Box 61, Folder 860)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Suranovic, Steven (Box 61, Folder 861)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Tschoegl, Adrian (Box 61, Folder 862)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Tsujimura, Natsuko (Box 61, Folder 863)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Wilson, Michiko (Box 61, Folder 864)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Parker, Joseph (Box 61, Folder 865)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Phillips, Quitman (Box 61, Folder 866)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Reichl, Christopher (Box 61, Folder 867)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Robbins, Donald (Box 61, Folder 868)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Sells, Peter (Box 61, Folder 869)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Maynard, Senko (Box 61, Folder 870)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - McDonald, Keiko (Box 61, Folder 871)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Muramatsu, Naoko (Box 61, Folder 872)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Nicholas, Donna (Box 61, Folder 873)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Orru, Marco (Box 61, Folder 874)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Koford, Kenneth (Box 61, Folder 875)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Krooth, Richard (Box 61, Folder 876)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 withdrawals - Linger, Daniel (Box 61, Folder 877)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Linowes, Richard (Box 61, Folder 878)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Mashima, Reiko (Box 61, Folder 879)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Ito, Kinko (Box 61, Folder 880)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 withdrawals - Kasza, Gregory (Box 61, Folder 881)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Kleeman, Faye Y. (Box 61, Folder 882)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Kleeman, Terry (Box 61, Folder 883)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Gelb, Joyce (Box 61, Folder 884)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Graybill, Maribeth (Box 61, Folder 885)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Hase, Michiko (Box 61, Folder 886)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Heine, Steven (Box 61, Folder 887)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Helgert, Joseph (Box 61, Folder 888)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Hoover, William (Box 61, Folder 889)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Houseman, Susan (Box 61, Folder 890)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Brock, Karen (Box 61, Folder 891)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 withdrawals - Campbell, David (Box 61, Folder 892)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Cheng, Mariah (Box 61, Folder 893)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Cline, Ann (Box 61, Folder 894)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Fung, Chi-Keung (Box 61, Folder 895)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Forsberg, Aaron (Box 61, Folder 896)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Furukai, Hiroshi (Box 61, Folder 897)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Gabriel, James (Box 61, Folder 898)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Research Planning Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Crystal, David (Box 61, Folder 899)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Research Planning Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Deng, Liping (Box 61, Folder 900)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Research Planning Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Jordan, Brenda and Nara, Hiroshi (Box 61, Folder 901)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Research Planning Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Kitagawa, Yoshihisa and Meulen, Alice ter (Box 61, Folder 902)